Matt: I'm very easily
distracted from things.
Particularly if I'm reading, I
can find myself reading words and
absolutely nothing is going in.
Probably because I've started
thinking about something else
or started interpreting a
particular phrase from earlier on.
That I, that can also happen
occasionally with speech.
I can have people say, ask me
perfectly intelligible questions or
say something absolutely coherent and
nothing comes out without getting no
semantic sense from it whatsoever.
And I have to ask them to repeat it,
sort of try and locate it from bits
and pieces of clues within that.
I do also have issues in terms of
managing, managing my own time.
Particularly if there are changes.
If I, if I'm moving from a at work period
or holiday period, or from holiday period
back into work, or you know, when we came
into lockdowns and working from home,
or if I've moved house or if there's any
big change that can throw my schedule for
quite a long time, things will fall out.
And I then gradually have to
build those things back in.
But I'm very inefficient.
I do try to keep a diary, but
again, that goes through periods
when it completely lapses.
There's also the issue with the
diary that you can be writing
things that are either...
writing things that are much too vague
to really makes sense of to interpret, or
you're trying to do too much at one time.
And so sometimes it's a case of
adjusting and getting clear and
realistic diary entries out of it.